- 邮寄的约一万封没有计数的投票... - 这也行
- from last week's presidential election... - Come on.
...于此人家中
...in the house of this man,
54岁的美国邮局职员万斯·奥特罗
54-year-old US postal worker Vance Otlow.
- 你看他 - 从去年邮局
- Look at this guy. - Otlow had grown more erratic
被梅耶邮政委员会关闭停业后
following post office closures last year
奥特罗变得十分不稳定
by the Meyer Postal Commission.
一万张票!
10,000 ballots!
还是个有着高度实用性
From a district with an
统计学价值经验的行政区
empirically high applied demography value.
你说的我一个字也没听懂
I don't know what you're saying,
不过你就继续做那些算术的东西 肯特
but you keep doing that math stuff, Kent,
- 就算谁用这事取笑你也不用管 - 好的 夫人
- no matter how much anyone makes fun of you, okay? - Yes, ma'am.
好极了 都听我说 凯伦
All right, listen. Karen
必须让这些票数得到承认 做得到么?
has got to get those ballots admitted, right?